One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Fight, crash through, and face the challenge!
These are our hard knock days.
Can't quench our thirst with a peaceful, everyday life.
Here we go - don't ever run away!
Let's go on living as the mighty winds take us!
We've still got so far to go.
Gotta keep going through the hard knock days.
Let's do it again, yes, baby. How many times
do I have to stand back up to make my dream come true?
Feels like the strength of my resolve
is put to the test everyday.
Hey, let's go!
I don't want to make excuses and settle for being mediocre.
We leapt into a crazy, lawless world.
As I struggled for a foothold, reality caught me off guard.
Even if it beats me, hits me, knocks me down again,
Oh!
Only when we get back on our feet and look forward,
will we have the last laugh, be the winners!
We gotta go down this glory road, till we reach our goal!
Fight, shake it off, act strong!
These are our hard knock days.
There's no such thing as a safe choice.
Here we go - we'll always be the strongest!
Let's keep moving - never mind the consequences.
Let's put our wishes all together,
and keep on going through the hard knock days.
Sabo's Adventure
Dressrosa
A Hill in the Eastern Town of Carta
Kyros' House
So you met him while with the Revolutionary Army?
Yes.
Luffy...
Robin, you don't have to wake him.
I just came to see his face before I set off.
Are you leaving the country already?
Yeah. Trouble's headed this way.
What kind of trouble?
CP-0.
They played a part in Doflamingo's deception scheme.
And they're targeting us.
Dressrosa's gonna get busy in a day or two.
You guys should also leave as soon as possible.
Thank you for telling us.
And what's more, I didn't know he had another brother besides Ace.
For real, this is the first I've heard of it.
I bet.
I think it surprised Luffy the most.
What do you mean by that?
I was presumed dead for a long time.
I was always with Luffy and Ace when I was a kid.
Running around with wild abandon,
being disciplined by that old man, Garp,
dreaming about becoming pirates...
And we exchanged cups of sake and became brothers.
But one day, I was involved in an accident.
Uh, well, an incident.
Ace! Luffy!
There's something wrong with this town! They're all mad!
They all know people are going to die, but they're acting like nothing's wrong. They're even smiling!
I don't want to be in this town!
I have to tell them as soon as possible!
Ace! Luffy! Run!
What happened to you, young boy?
This town smells worse than the Gray Terminal!
It's the disgusting stench of rotten people!
I'll never be free if I stay here!
Ace... Luffy...
I really want to see you...
This place is like a bird cage...
I'm not sure if I can bear living in
this kingdom, breathing this stale air.
Just what... is freedom?
Where can I find it?
Ace... Luffy...
Somebody... help me...
Help...
Vyou're late, Dragon!
How long did vyou plan to keep vus waiting?!
Sorry.
Vyou... What's that?
Th-This is awful!
You! Quickly, bring a doctor! This is an emergency!
Call the ship's doctor, quickly!
He's awake!
Please don't shock him.
Vi wasn't trying to do that!
Oh, vyou're so rude!
Huh?
Where am I?
You're on board our ship.
It says "Sabo" on your possessions. Is that your name?
Sabo?
Dunno.
"Dunno"? So what is vyour name, then?
No idea...
Don't tell me he's...
Most likely.
He still hasn't regained his memories?
Indeed, not even his own name.
I first met him in High Town, Goa Kingdom.
I'm certain he's one of the nobles from there.
Well, let's take him home then. Search for his parents...
No...
I don't wanna go back!
Why?
I dunno!
But...
that's the last thing I want!
So you've had amnesia up until two years ago?
Yeah.
If it was that serious,
just how did you get your memory back?
Ace helped me.
That's what I think, anyway.
Fire Fist Ace Dies
The timing couldn't have been any worse, but...
That was how...
...he woke me up.
Baltigo
Revolutionary Army General Headquarters
It's so hectic.
Oh, Chief Sabo! You came at the right time!
Report to the situation room at once!
The Paramount War between the Navy and the Whitebeard Pirates has ended!
Whitebeard lost?!
Is Iva-san alright?!
He's not listed among the casualties.
The dead include...
The Emperor, Whitebeard...
and...
Fire Fist Ace!
But more importantly, Dragon-san, this here...
Is it true?
Is Straw Hat Luffy your son?
Hmm?
Yes.
I'm gonna become a pirate...
...defeat everyone in my way, and be known worldwide!
That'll be proof enough that I once lived!
Sabo-kun, what's wrong?
You're acting weird!
Have you heard?
They say Akainu punched a hole right through his body!
When you exchange sake cups, you become brothers.
No matter where we are or what we do,
our bonds won't be broken!
So from now on, we're...
brothers!
Yeah!
Are you alright, Sabo?
Sabo-kun!
Sabo!
That's right...
This dead guy wasn't just some random pirate...
He wasn't just some threat in the
Pirate Era that needed to be eliminated!
Ace is my...
brother!
I won't run from, or lose to anyone!
The Chief of Staff''s awake!
Really? What a relief!
I thought you were gonna die, Sabo-kun!
You had quite a high fever, Sabo.
You were asleep for three days straight!
I was so worried!
Huh? You've got your memory back?
Yeah, I remember everything now.
Including who I am and why I
left home and sailed out to sea.
I see. Good for you.
Are you gonna quit the Revolutionary Army, then?!
Nope, no way.
Is Dragon-san still here?
Yeah.
There's something I want to talk about.
At that moment, I felt Ace say to me,
"You're Sabo. You're brothers with me and Luffy."
Finally... I've managed to come this far, Ace.
Check it out.
Luffy's started on his way again to become the Pirate King.
That's our little brother for you!
Headline: The Straw Hats Are Back
Sabo-kun?
I want you to ask a favor of
the entire Revolutionary Army.
There's a Devil Fruit that I need to acquire, no matter the cost.
Dressrosa
But, but Luffy-senpai...
What about the Flame Fruit?
There's someone I really don't want to have it,
but I got no choice.
My friends' lives are more important.
Ah'll definitely get ya the Flame Fruit!
Just go do whatever it was ya needed to!
Really? Thanks a bunch!
I won't let you have the Flame Fruit...
Straw Hat Luffy.
Hey, hey, hey! Who're you?
Why're you just casually talking to Luffy-senpai like that?
He's the younger brother of that legendary pirate, Fire Fist Ace-sama,
and the future Pirate King, you dumbass!
I've known that for a long time.
What's your problem?!
Just showing up outta nowhere and telling me
you won't let me have the Flame Fruit!
It's me, Luffy.
What do you mean, "It's me"?!
Get this! The Flame Fruit is a keepsake of Ace's!
If you want it, we're enemies!
And as for you calling me "Luffy"...
See this beard?
I'm Lucy!
You really think I wouldn't know my little brother's face behind that disguise of his?
"Little brother"?
Look here, the only people allowed to call me "little brother"...
are Ace, who's dead, and...
a guy who died way earlier...
Sabo!
You can't be him!
We stole a bottle of sake from Dadan and made a toast...
Sabo!
What the hell?! Where have you been this whole time?!
I thought you were dead!
Thank you, Luffy!
I'm glad you lived!
But Sabo, I...
I let Ace be killed right in front of me...
I know. Even though Ace died, I'm...
so happy that you survived!
I almost lost both of my brothers without being able to do a thing!
If you'd died too, I would've been left on my own!
So, thanks!
Thanks for staying alive, Luffy!
Is it alright if I eat the Flame Fruit?
Uh-huh!
That'd be great! Nobody else can have it!
That darn Luffy... He's smiling!
Makes you wonder what he's dreaming about.
Well, I'm off.
So soon?
I got to see his face, so...
Here, I had a Vivre Card made from Luffy, just in case.
Oh? When'd you have time for that?
I'll be taking a piece.
Alright. Luffy may be a bit of a handful,
but please take good care of him.
Yeah! You can count on us!
He and Ace said the same thing.
Sabo, that you? Hack here.
Yeah, I just left. I'll be back soon.
Roger that.
So, how'd it go? Luffy-kun was quite...
Why'd he hang up?!
That selfish jerk!
Whoa there, Hack-san!
We're all set to depart, right?
Yeah, anytime.
Alright!
Once we return to Baltigo, there's so much I have to tell Dragon-san about Luffy!
I really am...
glad I got to see him again.
Let's move out!
Dressrosa
What is it? Could you look for me?
It's a "one".
I see. The only side that would be in Straw Hat's favor...
That's what we agreed upon, yes?
Yes, it is, but...
Then, he won this one.
We shan't arrest him tonight.
You can't determine that just by a roll of the die, Isshou-san!
We ran all over the entire country and finally found out where he is!
After all the disrespect you showed Fleet Admiral Sakazuki...
If we want to take down Law and Straw Hat, now's our chance!
Maynard-san!
A man ought not complain after the die is cast.
Quite pathetic of you, really.
Royal Palace
Has anyone seen Lucy after all that?
No, nobody did.
I just wanna thank him!
There's already quite a fuss out there.
Even if they truly are pirates or criminals,
they're unquestionably our saviors.
Grandfather!
Rebecca.
Father, Lucy, and the others aren't here at the Palace!
Ah, don't worry about that. Kyros called.
They're all together.
I see.
That aside...
Rebecca.
If I were to return as king,
that would make you a princess.
The Next Day
The New World
(The Twirly Hat Pirates)
Damn!
We finally shook off Big Mom's ship
after all that trouble...
So why would you get us into even more trouble?!
You've no say in the matter!
Do as you're told!
I'm saying it for the sake of you guys!
Don't stick your nose in their business!
We should have waited patiently on the ship.
You're pretty stupid to be rushing ahead like this!
Shut up and do what I tell you!
You gonna do it?!
Or would you rather I crush your heart?!
Fine! But I won't forget this.
It was the right call to come ashore!
We can still save them! We need your help!
In that case, why don't you treat me more nicely...
You say something?!
Stop threatening me with that!
Hurry up, Caesar!
Stop telling me what to do, you blasted raccoon dog!
I'm a reindeer!
What's the difference?!
Shut up! Just hurry up!
If they die because of you, I'll make you pay for it!
We need your help!
It's hard to run here!
I can't believe we were separated
from Sanji-san and the others.
We're in trouble!
We were too captivated by the mystery girl.
Oh, watch out, Nami-san!
Watch out, me!
No, how could you?!
How could you?! How could you?!
Onami, they are upon us!
Yahoo!
Is this it, invaders?
Hey! Where'd you hide that girl?
How'd you guys make it onto this island?
Answer me! This place is pretty hard to-
What... what's going on?!
What is it this time?!
It's a Rain-Ruption!
Again?
Get down!
What is that?!
"Rain"?
That's way off! It's a deluge!
I shall protect you no matter what!
No!
Nami-san!
Momonosuke-san!
Help me!
Assist me, too!
Geez!
You Devil Fruit users are such pains in the butt!
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you!
You won't get away from me, you damned invaders!
Come on, pull yourself together!
Thank you, as always.
You too, Momo!
I am in your debt.
When in doubt...
Just kill!
Brook!
Sir Bones!
I finally managed to protect you!
Please allow me to handle the rest!
Tsk! How arrogant!
Sheep's Horn!
What?!
What are those arms?
Sir Bones!
Take this!
Soul Parade!
Sir Bones, that is amazing!
What manner of ability is this?
Brook!
Keep stalling him!
Diable Mouton...
Shot!
Sheepshead-sama!
Sanji-kun!
Oh, Nami-swan!
Who are you people?!
And just who are you people...
What? How creepy!
Ginrummy-sama!
You lot there! Retreat!
Sheepshead-sama has been done in!
What?!
But we haven't found the samurai yet!
We've cornered them this far,
and he still hasn't shown himself!
"The samurai's not here." Tell him exactly that!
Yes, ma'am!
The water's draining away...
What was that all about, I wonder?
It's certainly one strange island.
I hope that girl's okay, too...
She's more agile than we are. She'll be quite alright.
You're right.
Hey, guys!
Get over here right now!
That be Chop'emon, in the lower forest!
Then let's move out! There's no time to lose!
The Kid Pirates' Safe House
What's that noise?
What happened?
Captain, there's a massive hole!
A hole?
Something's landed!
Take arms!
Yeah!
That's it!
It certainly is quite large.
Where did it fall from?
Just who in the hell caused this?!
Hey, doesn't it look human-shaped?
If I recall correctly...
There's a legend about a sky island where some monster lives...
Somewhere in the sky, around here, right?
Are you telling me that it was pushed off of a sky island?!
Captain Kid!
One of our ships was capsized by the impact!
What'd you say?!
Damn it all! Who did this?!
The strong live, and the weak die.
That is just how the world is.
A few minutes ago...
Sky Island - The Ruins of Balloon Terminal
What exactly are you doing?
Let us leave him be, High Priest!
He must be insane!
We're ten thousand meters up in the air.
This man was looking for a place to die.
If he's serious, why bother to stop him?
To sum up his life,
he had been defeated seven times as a pirate,
and was captured by the Navy or his enemies eighteen times.
He underwent torture repeatedly, and lived as a criminal.
He wanted to commit suicide...
in an extraordinary way by jumping off of a sky island.
Hence, the current situation.
It bears repeating:
Single-handedly, he challenged
the Navy and the Emperors,
was captured eighteen times,
and sentenced to death forty times.
When hanged, the chain broke.
When put under the guillotine,
the blade shattered.
When sentenced to impalement,
the spear splintered.
Consequently, he sank nine prison ships.
In short, no one could kill him.
And that included himself.
What is it now?
What the hell is that monster?
Damn, my head hurts.
Guess it's hard to die.
I survived again.
I'm impressed he pulled it off...
That old man, Whitebeard.
The man searching for his deathbed:
Kaidou of the Beasts
People say, "If it's one-on-one, Kaidou will win."
Whether on land, sea, or air, he is the pirate known as "the mightiest being alive".
I've no choice, have I?!
Damn it all!
Hurry up, Joker!
Make ready for the final battle!
I don't care if this boring world is laid to waste!
Let's start the greatest war the world's ever seen!